Bluetooth
ICICI Lombard's quarter two
numbers were already out, we
will talk about the same in this video and will know whether you should make a
new investment in ICICI Lombard
or not. Let's start,
see here the company has declared a difference of Rs 4, that is,
if you have a
hundred years end, you will get a difference of ₹400 here,
you can calculate accordingly,
if we talk about revenue, that is, the
income etc. that you get, the
premium that they get, then
there is a decline of about 0.6 percent
available, almost or visible
revenue was available on a quarterly basis,
but if we talk about profitability, then the
profitability increased by 129 percent here, and the
total net profit of the company was Rs 6 crore, the
last quarter was also
any 1022 claim for Virat, on the one hand,
health insurance etc., so the amount of 1 liter had become
quite high and  The
profitability of the second company had reduced, that is,
normally Rs. 350 to
400 crores every quarter. Here,
ICICI Lombard makes a profit of Rs. 350 to 400 crores, but there has been nothing
unusual here, let
me tell you this, but if we
talk about the revenue numbers on this near future, then
we saw a growth of 232%
in the online website numbers here. Firstly, the
revenue numbers on this near future are good,
but the profitability here increased by just one percent and the
total net profit of the company came to Rs. 6 crores here. So,
if you look at the revenue point,
things are good, but the profit
margin here is less, in my
opinion, it could have disturbed the market a bit. Look,
I think the
entire chapter is so deeply
penetrated, but you have to understand
that when the entire sector is Family and
President, that is, this entire chapter is growing
day to day, but the one thing that I
see as a mild concern here is that there are too
many form questions.
Look at ICICI Bank, which has
more than 5 lakh savings accounts, then
they will have to choose the big bank only, so
if you see directly, if your bank is
with one bank account, if you have
insurance etc. then many things will be available for you, so this is what will happen
in my kitchen today,
my work will be seen happening here, in my long-term mind, I do
not see anything here, okay,
this company has a market cap of about 600 crores, but
about 60%, so in the last
quarter, there was a profit of 200 crores,
this is the result, after this, the period of about 40 to
45 years will come, this
entire industry is going to give a little market premium
relation, so in the coming time, the
penetration is increasing in India,
there, this police tractor,
all what is the full, for the last four years, there has been a
continuous decline in the revenue numbers
and for the last four years, the
profitability of the company has also been
big and even now, this near Dixit
number has revenue.  We are also seeing growth, the
profitability of the company is increasing,
now look at this stock at 1505, right now
its all-time high of about 1676 is almost
touched and you should obtain stock, right now
you are getting it at a discount, okay, I
think the numbers are good, but the hair and
this net profit in between is a
bit disappointing, this is a key
growth of 2 percent seen here, it remains to be
seen how the market reacts to it, mother cut, for long term
investors there are some fundamental
changes here, it is not like that at all, you stay tuned
if you want to invest, I
think you can definitely invest,
if we talk about general insurance,
which is listed securities,
this company is quite good and prevention
measures have backed by many good banks, a
private bank with job license,
this bad feeling prevalence and
there is a drop in the trend of
factors,
you must have known everything about ICICI Lombard's quarter two numbers,
if  Please comment on any of your
queries, I will definitely
reply to your comment. So,
thank you. Have a nice day ahead.